How about you?
Feel like fighting?
No thanks, pal.
My magic skill's gonna reach 900
soon, so I'd rather not die just yet.
At least you're honest about it.
How about you, miss?
Guess I'll pass, too.
But next time, you're going down! Oh.
Then next time, I'll make sure
to bring more friends along.
I'm not going to see
you in the next episode.
I'm not going to say that
I'm still going to say that.
I'm still going to hear
you in the
next episode.
Hey, what's up with those flames?
There remain lights.
The players you killed can still hear you.
Okay, now we can talk.
So, what do you want?
You want me to thank you?
Run away?
Or do you want to fight?
Hmm.
If we break down what just happened, it's
one of those knight in shining armor.
saves the princess moments.
Huh?
You could burst into tears
and throw your arms around me.
Oh, piss off, loser!
Nah, I was just kidding.
No way!
It won't let her do that!
Watch it! Stay out of sight!
Mommy and me are the only
ones allowed to hug Daddy!
Wait, Daddy?
What?
Nothing, no.
No way.
Is that one of those private pixies?
Uh, sort of, I guess.
Mm-hmm.
Then how about you tell me what a Spriggan
like you is doing wandering around here.
I guess I got lost.
How could you get that lost?
Spriggan territory's way to the east.
God, you're weird.
Anyway, thank you for saving me.
I guess I should introduce myself.
I'm Leafa.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kirito, and this is Yui.
Okay then, Kirito, do
you have any plans today?
I mean, because if you don't, I
can buy you a drink as thanks.
A drink sounds awesome,
and if you don't mind,
I'd like to pick your
brain about some stuff.
Like, what kind of stuff?
Just more about this world,
and especially about the tree.
Oh, you mean the world tree?
Yeah, sure.
I might not look like it.
but I know a lot about this game.
There's this neutral
village to the north of us.
It's a little out of the
way, but we can fly there.
Okay, but what about Sylvain?
Isn't that town closer to us?
You really don't know
anything about this game.
Sylvain is Sylph territory. So?
You're not a sylph.
If you're in their territory, you can't
attack them, but they can attack you.
As long as I don't do anything to
provoke them, no one will attack me.
And you'll be there, Miss Leafa.
Just call me Leafa, and if you really
want to go there, I'll take you.
I can't guarantee your safety, though.
Let's get flying!
Wait, you mean you can fly
without using the controller?
Of course, can't you?
I just learned how to use this thing, so
I'm still trying to figure everything out.
Well, there's a little trick to doing it.
Come on, turn around, but
don't access your controller.
Okay.
Can you feel where my
hand is touching you?
Mm-hmm.
Imagine you've got virtual bones and
muscles here spreading out into your wings.
Then try and move them.
Virtual bones and muscles.
Yeah, just like that.
You got it!
Okay, now try doing the
same thing, only harder.
Oh no! Daddy! Gidito! Are you okay?
How do I make it stop?
Daddy, that's hilarious.
Wow, this is awesome.
I know, right?
Looks like you're starting
to get the hang of it.
Now, follow me! Okay!
Take it slow until you get better at it.
Don't worry about me.
We can go faster.
Okay.
Huh? Huh?
Is that as fast as you can go?
Well, don't blame me if you crash.
I can't go on, I need a break!
You're the only person I know who
can handle flying at this speed.
We made it!
Hey, we're gonna land at the
base of the central tower, okay?
Wait, Kirito, you do
know how to land, right?
No, not really.
Uh...
Oh, crap.
Too late now.
You're on your own!
Wait, what?
You're kidding me!
That was so not cool.
Stop whining already.
I can heal you.
Sue, Fila, Haedel, Astolu.
No way!
This is magic?
The Undine are the only ones who
specialize in high-level healing spells.
But that's an important one anyone
can do, so you should learn it.
Different races have
different skills, huh?
Does the Spriggan race have
anything they're good at?
Well, you guys are good at treasure
hunting and illusion magic.
Neither of those things are
much help in battle, though.
So this is a sylph town.
Man, it's beautiful.
I know, right?
Lipa!
Thank God you're okay!
Oh, hey, Recon.
I knew you'd survive.
Spriggan!
No, it's okay.
He saved me from those salamanders.
This is my friend.
His name's Recon.
Hey there.
My name's Kirito.
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Wait, what am I talking about?
I take that back.
You sure about him?
He could be a spy or something.
No, he's cool.
I'm pretty sure if he really was a
spy, he wouldn't be such a Tetsuo.
Gee, thanks a lot.
Anyway, Sigurd and the others are
waiting for you at the tavern.
Oh, that's right.
On second thought, I can't go today. Huh?
You're not going? Nope.
I sort of promised Kirito I'd
buy him a drink for saving me.
See you later!
Wait, you don't have to...
Oh, Lipia!
Is that retcon guy your boyfriend?
Yeah, are the two of you in love?
No!
We're not in love!
but we're just in the same party is all.
I don't know, from where I was
standing, you guys seemed tight.
Whatever, I know him in real life.
We go to the same school and
we're classmates, but that's it.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, bottoms up.
And thanks again for saving me.
Those guys in the forest
were playing pretty rough.
Are Gangs of PKers normal
for this game or what?
Well, for one thing, the salamander
and sylph races never got along.
But those guys were organized, and
that wasn't happening until recently.
I don't know.
If you ask me, they're gearing up
to try to clear the world tree soon.
Actually, I was hoping you could tell
me what you knew about the world tree.
Oh, yeah, you mentioned it before.
Why do you want to know?
I want to get to the top as soon as I can.
Join the club.
Every player wants to get to the top.
You could say that's the
grand quest of Alfheim Online.
What do you mean?
You know how you're limited
in how high you can fly?
The fact is,
none of the races can fly continuously
for more than ten minutes at a time.
However,
at the top of the tree is the floating city,
and in it lives Oberon, the Fairy King.
The first race to reach him will be reborn
as an advanced class of
fairy known as Alves.
And what's cool about that is they'll be
able to fly around for
as long as they want.
That is cool.
It'd be sweet to fly
for as long as I want.
So how does someone get to
the top of the tree at the
base of the tree there's a
big dome that's the gateway
to the floating city but
then you have to get past the
npcs that guard it and
they're super powerful they're
that strong huh let me
put it this way the game's
been around for a year now
right no one's got past them
maybe everyone's missed that
one key quest no wait maybe
it's designed so that one
race can't reach it alone hey
you got good instincts for
now everyone seems to think
it's a missing quest so
they're out there looking for
it but if we have to work
together to beat it it'll
never happen why not because
it doesn't make sense why
would you help another race
with a quest if they're
the ones who get the reward
can you imagine anyone being
cool with that arrangement
then getting to the top of
the tree is impossible what's
the point in even trying?
No arguments here!
Flying is pretty addictive though.
Once you get a taste for it.
You can't give it up You think
even if it takes years someday,
but I can't wait around that long!
Daddy
Sorry, it's just that I have to get to the
top of the world tree as soon as I can.
Okay, what's the rush?
I'm sort of looking for someone.
What do you mean?
No offense, but it's hard to explain.
Thank you, Leafa.
All the info you gave
me is really gonna help.
Wait, are you heading for
the World Tree right now?
Uh-huh, I need to see for myself
Alone?
That's crazy
It's really far away and
you'll have to fight a
bunch of monsters I know you
can handle yourself, but...
Hey, if you want, I can take you there.
Thanks, but we just met, and I wouldn't
feel right you coming all that way.
Right, then maybe you already
know how to get there.
What you gonna do about the Guardians?
Well, I'll think of
something when I get there.
Too late.
My mind's made up.
Okay.
So, do you want to meet up tomorrow?
Yeah, sure.
Then I'll meet you here
tomorrow at 3 p .m.
sharp.
Um, I have to log out now.
So when you're ready, you can log out
in one of the rooms upstairs, okay?
Well, see you then. Wait!
Thank you, Leafa.
You:
Hey, if you want, I can take you there.
Talk about a weird guy!
Kirito...
I guess this means goodbye
till tomorrow, doesn't it?
Yeah, but I'll be back soon.
It won't be that long.
Daddy?
Would it be alright if
I slept next to you?
Just until you log out?
Yeah, sure, I don't mind.
You and me, we're gonna save Asuna.
Then we'll all go buy a
house somewhere again.
That would make me so happy.
You know, living with you and Mommy
again would be a dream come true.
It's not a dream.
I promise you I'll make it a reality.
Good night, Daddy.
Right now, your face is more
beautiful than anything, Titania.
The way you look like you're about to cry.
I wish I could preserve it
and hang it up on a wall.
What are you waiting for?
Permission?
You can do whatever you want.
I have no say in the matter.
You're the system admin, after all.
Such cold words from such a pretty mouth.
Now, have I ever laid a hand on you
when you didn't want me to, Titania?
Stop calling me by that stupid name.
My name is Asuna. Sugo.
You're spoiling the fun.
In this world, I'm known
as Oberon the Fairy King.
There's not a player who wouldn't give
everything to be the ruler of Alfheim.
And you are Queen Titania,
my breathtaking bride.
What more could you ask for?
So, as my queen, as my bride, when
will you give your heart to me?
Never.
The only things I'll give you are
disgust and hatred, and nothing more.
You're a stubborn girl,
I'll give you that.
But you know, for a while
now I've been thinking.
Romance is nice and all, but it might
be more fun if I just took you by force.
Stop it!
Of course, my dear. It was a joke.
I'd never really force myself on you.
I don't have to.
You'll start wanting me
soon enough, I promise.
You're insane.
You won't be talking like
that for much longer.
Right now, in this world, Tens of thousands
of players are enjoying this game.
But none of them have a clue about the
true potential of the full-dive system.
Did you know that by expanding
the brain's control regions,
one could influence a person's
thoughts, emotions, and memories?
You can't!
Technology like that is illegal!
Oh, but you're wrong.
In fact, several countries are
researching it as we speak.
The only thing standing in the way
is finding people to experiment on.
But one day, I was watching
the news, and there they were.
Ten thousand ideal guinea pigs!
Mr.
Kayaba was a genius,
but he was also a fool.
All he wanted to use his
technology for was his game.
He couldn't see the potential in it.
But I did.
It wasn't too difficult
to adjust the routers.
The minute SAO's players were logged
out, I just grabbed a few from the flow.
Just like that, I had 300 of
my very own test subjects.
My research has taken great
strides the past two months.
I've been developing a
technology that seeds memories
with objects and uses
them to control emotion.
My work is almost finished now.
You are crazy.
My father would never allow
that kind of research.
He wouldn't if he knew about it,
but it's being done in secret—just
a small team and myself.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't be able to sell it off
to who an American corporation
you won't believe how anxious
they are to get their hands on it,
and soon I'm going to sell it and
wreck to them for as much as I can.
That won't happen; I'll see to that as
soon as I get back to the real world.
world The first thing I'll do
is report you to the police.
You want to bet?
You're in the same boat
as the other guinea pigs.
What, you haven't figured it out?
If I wanted, I could
alter your memories, too.
I'm on the way.
Wait for my orders.
Don't worry.
The last thing I'd ever want to do
is turn you into a porcelain doll.
But the next time we
meet, I hope you'll be...
just a bit more submissive.
Titania.
Farewell, my love.
Kirito, please save me.
I love you.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.